tastelessgentlemen.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy - The Tasteless Gentlemen

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.  
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Editorial Rules

We reserve the right to edit any and all content as needed, for any reason, at any time.  
Values on Politics, Content, and Overall Experience

All voices and opinions are welcome. Everyone has their own views and are welcome to share them on TTG. Remember that not everyone has the same views, so be respectful to each other and engage in friendly debate within comment sections if you please.  
It’s OK to disagree with people while engaging in meaningful conversation.  
We wish to provide fun, factual, and conversational content to give readers an enjoyable user experience with content worth sharing.  
Write something amazing filled with facts and useful information and it will perform much better. Articles with no facts or personality will perform poorly or may not be approved. If you tell a great story, then people will share it.

## Site Cookies

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit[http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete MagOne cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.)

MagOne does not use cookies via the Blogger-based markup of this site, or in posts and pages. However, third party vendors whose advertisements are placed on this website may use cookies or web beacons. Details of these vendors are provided below.

## Third Party and Advertiser Cookies

MagOne has no access to or control over these cookies!

### Google Analytics

We use this to understand how the site is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is all anonymous.

You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at <http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

### Google Adsense

This cookie is used by Google to report to us how the adverts shown on MagOne are performing. User data is all anonymous.

You can find out more generally about Google and its policies and principles as regards advertising at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>
